<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">HiHi</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    
    <string-array name="categories">
        <item>Cupcake</item>
        <item>Chocolate</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="titles0">
        <item>Maffins</item>
        <item>Tiramisu</item>
        <item>Pancakes</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="titles1">
        <item>Kitkat</item>
        <item>Snickers</item>
        <item>Merci</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="titles2">
        <item>Pizza</item>
        <item>Hot dogs</item>
        <item>Cheeseburger</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="titles0articles">
        <item>The term muffin typically refers to an individual sized quick bread product which can be sweet or savory. The typical American muffin is similar to a cupcake in size and cooking methods. These can come in both savory varieties, such as corn or cheese muffins, or sweet varieties such as blueberry or banana.

Muffin also refers to a flatter disk-shaped bread of English origin, commonly referred to as an English muffin outside the United Kingdom. These muffins are also popular in Commonwealth countries and the United States.</item>
        <item>Tiramisu (from Italian, spelled tiramisù, [tiɾamiˈsu], meaning "pick me up" or "lift me up") is a popular coffee-flavoured Italian dessert. It is made of ladyfingers (Italian: Savoiardi, [savoˈjardi]) dipped in coffee, layered with a whipped mixture of eggs, sugar and mascarpone cheese, flavoured with cocoa. </item>
        <item> Pancake is a flat cake, often thin, and round, prepared from a starch-based batter and cooked on a hot surface such as a griddle or frying pan. In Britain, pancakes are often unleavened, and resemble a crêpe.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="titles1articles">
        <item>About Merci</item>
        <item>Snickers is a brand name chocolate bar made by Mars, Incorporated. It consists of nougat topped with caramel and peanuts, enrobed in milk chocolate.[1] Snickers has annual global sales of $2 billion</item>
        <item>Merci is a brand of German chocolate candy manufactured by the German company August Storck KG.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="titles2articles">
        <item>The modern pizza was invented in Naples, Italy, and the dish and its variants have since become popular in many parts of the world.</item>
        <item>About Hot dog </item>
        <item>About Cheeseburger</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
